For the Bible Tells Me So is a documentary film directed by Daniel Karslake.
An exploration of the intersection between
religion and homosexuality in the U.S.
and how the religious right has used its interpretation of
the Bible to stigmatize the gay community.
Self, played by Imogene Robinson.
Self, played by Victor Robinson.
Self (as V. Gene Robinson), played by Gene Robinson.
Self, played by Isabella 'Boo' McDaniel.
Self - Founder, Soul Force, played by Mel White.
Self, played by Dick Gephardt.
For the Bible Tells Me So is a 2007 American
documentary film directed by Daniel G.
Karslake about homosexuality and its perceived conflict with Christianity, as well as
various interpretations of what the Bible says about sexual orientation.
The film premiered at the 2007 Sundance Film Festival.
The film explores themes of bible, male homosexuality, religion.